<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--
   <string name="name"></string>
   <string name="desc"></string>
   <string name="purpose"></string>
   <string name="overview"></string>
   <string-array name="includes">
       <item></item>
   </string-array>
   -->

    <!-- Understanding Your Communication Style -->
    <string name="understand_comm_style_title">Understanding Your Communication Style</string>
    <string name="understand_comm_style_desc">This project focuses on recognizing your preferred communication style and understanding how your style impacts your interactions with others.</string>
    <string name="understand_comm_style_purpose">The purpose of this project is to learn about different communication styles and identify your primary style.</string>
    <string name="understand_comm_style_overview">Complete the Discover Your Communication Style questionnaire to help you identify your style. Deliver a 5- to 7-minute speech at a club meeting about your communication style and its impact on your professional and/or personal relationships. If you are uncomfortable discussing your communication style, you may speak about the communication styles you have encountered and how they impact you. Your speech should not be a report of the content of this project.</string>
    <string-array name="understand_comm_style_includes">
        <item>The Discover Your Communication Style questionnaire</item>
        <item>A 5- to 7-minute speech</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Understanding Your Leadership Style -->
    <string name="understand_lead_style_title">Understanding Your Leadership Style</string>
    <string name="understand_lead_style_desc">This project is designed to introduce the different styles of leadership and help you identify your preferred style.</string>
    <string name="understand_lead_style_purpose">The purpose of this project is to identify your primary leadership style or styles.</string>
    <string name="understand_lead_style_overview">Complete the Discover Your Leadership Style questionnaire. Consider how your leadership style impacts the people around you and how you can adjust it to more effectively lead people with styles different from your own. Deliver a 5- to 7-minute speech at a club meeting to share some aspect of your leadership style or leadership styles in general. You may choose to discuss your style preferences when working with others, your style and how you can adapt it to situations, or leadership styles in general and how they impact a group.</string>
    <string-array name="understand_lead_style_includes">
        <item>The Discover Your Leadership Style questionnaire</item>
        <item>A 5- to 7-minute speech</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Introduction to Toastmasters Mentoring -->
    <string name="intro_toast_mentor_title">Introduction to Toastmasters Mentoring</string>
    <string name="intro_toast_mentor_desc">This project introduces the value of mentorship and the Toastmasters view of mentors and proteges.</string>
    <string name="intro_toast_mentor_purpose">The purpose of this project is to clearly define how Toastmasters envisions mentoring.</string>
    <string name="intro_toast_mentor_overview">Write and present a 5- to 7-minute speech about a time when you were a protégé. Share the impact and importance of having a mentor. This speech is not a report on the content of this project.</string>
    <string-array name="intro_toast_mentor_includes">
        <item>A 5- to 7-minute speech</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>