<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Pathways List-->
    <string name="pathname_dynamic_leadership">Dynamic Leadership</string>
    <string name="pathname_effective_coaching">Effective Coaching</string>
    <string name="pathname_innovative_planning">Innovative Planning</string>
    <string name="pathname_leadership_development">Leadership Development</string>
    <string name="pathname_motivational_strategies">Motivational Strategies</string>
    <string name="pathname_persuasive_influence">Persuasive Influence</string>
    <string name="pathname_presentation_mastery">Presentation Mastery</string>
    <string name="pathname_strategic_relationships">Strategic Relationships</string>
    <string name="pathname_team_collaboration">Team Collaboration</string>
    <string name="pathname_visionary_communication">Visionary Communication</string>

    <!-- Logo Content Descriptions -->
    <string name="cont_desc_dynamic_leadership_logo">Dynamic Leadership Pathways Logo</string>
    <string name="cont_desc_effective_coaching_logo">Effective Coaching Pathways Logo</string>
    <string name="cont_desc_innovative_planning_logo">Innovative Planning Pathways Logo</string>
    <string name="cont_desc_leadership_development_logo">Leadership Development Pathways Logo</string>
    <string name="cont_desc_motivational_strategies_logo">Motivational Strategies Pathways Logo</string>
    <string name="cont_desc_persuasive_influence_logo">Persuasive Influence Pathways Logo</string>
    <string name="cont_desc_presentation_mastery_logo">Presentation Mastery Pathways Logo</string>
    <string name="cont_desc_strategic_relationships_logo">Strategic Relationships Pathways Logo</string>
    <string name="cont_desc_team_collaboration_logo">Team Collaboration Pathways Logo</string>
    <string name="cont_desc_visionary_communication_logo">Visionary Communication Pathways Logo</string>

    <!-- Pathways Path Description -->
    <string name="pathdesc_dynamic_leadership">
        This path helps you build your skills as a strategic leader.
        The projects on this path focus on understanding leadership and communication styles,
        the effect of conflict on a group and the skills needed to defuse and direct conflict.
        These projects also emphasize the development of strategies to facilitate change in an
        organization or group, interpersonal communication and public speaking. This path
        culminates in a project focused on applying your leadership skills.
    </string>
    <string name="pathdesc_effective_coaching">
        This path helps you build your skills as a positive communicator and leader. The projects on
        this path focus on understanding and building consensus, contributing to the development of
        others by coaching and establishing strong public speaking skills. Each project emphasizes the
        importance of effective interpersonal communication. This path culminates in a
        “High Performance Leadership” project of your design.
    </string>
    <string name="pathdesc_innovative_planning">
        This path helps you build your skills as a public speaker and leader. The projects on this path
        focus on developing a strong connection with audience members when you present, speech writing
        and speech delivery. The projects contribute to building an understanding of the steps to manage
        a project, as well as creating innovative solutions. This path culminates in a
        “High Performance Leadership” project of your design.
    </string>
    <string name="pathdesc_leadership_development">
        This path helps you build your skills as an effective communicator and leader. The projects on
        this path focus on learning how to manage time, as well as how to develop and implement a plan.
        Public speaking and leading a team are emphasized in all projects. This path culminates in the
        planning and execution of an event that will allow you to apply everything you learned.
    </string>
    <string name="pathdesc_motivational_strategies">
        This path helps you build your skills as a powerful and effective communicator. The projects focus
        on learning strategies for building connections with the people around you, understanding motivation
        and successfully leading small groups to accomplish tasks. This path culminates in a comprehensive
        team-building project that brings all of your skills together—including public speaking.
    </string>
    <string name="pathdesc_persuasive_influence">
        This path helps you build your skills as an innovative communicator and leader. The projects on this
        path focus on how to negotiate a positive outcome together with building strong interpersonal communication
        and public speaking skills. Each project emphasizes developing leadership skills to use in complex situations,
        as well as creating innovative solutions to challenges. This path culminates in a “High Performance Leadership”
        project of your design.
    </string>
    <string name="pathdesc_presentation_mastery">
        This path helps you build your skills as an accomplished public speaker. The projects on this path focus
        on learning how an audience responds to you and improving your connection with audience members. The
        projects contribute to developing an understanding of effective public speaking technique, including speech
        writing and speech delivery. This path culminates in an extended speech that will allow you to apply what
        you learned.
    </string>
    <string name="pathdesc_strategic_relationships">
        This path helps you build your skills as a leader in communication. The projects on this path focus on
        understanding diversity, building personal and/or professional connections with a variety of people and
        developing a public relations strategy. Communicating well interpersonally and as a public speaker is
        emphasized in each project. The path culminates in a project to apply your skills as a leader in a
        volunteer organization.
    </string>
    <string name="pathdesc_team_collaboration">
        This path helps you build your skills as a collaborative leader. The projects on this path focus on active
        listening, motivating others and collaborating with a team. Each project contributes to building interpersonal
        communication and public speaking skills. This path culminates in a project focused on applying your leadership
        skills.
    </string>
    <string name="pathdesc_visionary_communication">
        This path helps you build your skills as a strategic communicator and leader. The projects on this path focus
        on developing your skills for sharing information with a group, planning communications and creating innovative
        solutions. Speech writing and speech delivery are emphasized in each project. This path culminates in the
        development and launch of a long-term personal or professional vision.
    </string>

    <string-array name="path_quotes">
        <item>"A leader is best when people barely know he exists, when his work is done, his aim fulfilled, they will say: we did it ourselves."</item>
        <item>"I think the most important thing about coaching is that you have to have a sense of confidence about what you're doing."</item>
        <item>"In preparing for battle I have always found that plans are useless, but planning is indispensable."</item>
        <item>"Leaders aren\'t born, they are made. And they are made just like anything else, through hard work. And that's the price we'll have to pay to achieve that goal, or any goal."</item>
        <item>"Success… seems to be connected with action. Successful people keep moving. They make mistakes, but they don’t quit."</item>
        <item>"Influence is when you are not the one talking and yet your words fill the room; when you are absent and yet your presence is felt everywhere."</item>
        <item>"To talk well and eloquently is a very great art, but that an equally great one is to know the right moment to stop."</item>
        <item>"You can make more friends in two months by becoming interested in other people than you can in two years by trying to get other people interested in you."</item>
        <item>"Coming together is a beginning. Keeping together is progress. Working together is success."</item>
        <item>"Good leaders must communicate vision clearly, creatively, and continually. However, the vision doesn't come alive until the leader models it."</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>